Hello everyone, we are Takamine Nadeshiko!
Let me introduce myself right away.
Let's start with Saa-chan.
I'm Saora Ryuki.
I'm Hina Inada.
I'm Erisa Higashiyama.
I'm Nao Kizuki
I am Soo Suzumi
I am Lili Haru
I am Mikuru Hoshitani
I am Momona Matsumoto
I am Himeri Umiyama
Yes, we are Takamine no Nadeshiko National Invitational Tour 2023 First Trip!
We've been to four places so far.
How is everyone doing?
Oh, man!
I know, right?
We've lost so much!
Only two more to go.
It's almost over.
Do I have to remind you?
Remind you?
Go to your hometown, Osaka.
Osaka.
I'm so happy.
How about you, Rii-chan?
But I've been to so many places.
Time passed so fast.
I was so happy to be able to eat some of the local food, like soup.
There are only two more shows left.
The next show will be in Nagoya on June 18.
The next show will be in Nagoya on June 18, and my partner for the show will be Team Sachi.
This time, Team Sachi is coming!
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Now I would like to invite them to join us.
Team Sachi, please.
Congratulations!
Good day to you. See you again.
I'm going to interrupt.
Please say hello.
We, Seino!
Super Tan Strong Energy Positive Exciting Soul From Nagoya
Team Sharky!
Please say hello.
Please give us your best regards.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you.
I'm glad to meet you.
I would like to get to know you better.
I will be on trial on June 18, and I would like to get to know you better,
Today, I would like to make a plan to get to know you better, Team Sachi.
Yay!
Let's get to know each other!
Let's get to know each other.
Let's get to know each other better, so today, we would like to plan a party for you.
A shish-kebab party!
Yay!
Marie?
We'll have shish-kebabs and all the drinks you can drink.
Thank you very much!
I look forward to getting to know Team Orca better as we eat and drink!
I look forward to getting to know you better!
I'm red-collared because I'd like to get to know you better!
Okay, well, nice to meet you, Team Orca, please introduce yourself!
Let's go one by one!
Yes, I'm Haruna Tebasaki Midori Sakamoto!
Please call me Haruka Haru-chan! Please call me Haruka Haru-chan!
Yes, I'm Honoka Akimoto, Nagoya Red!
Please call me Ho-chan!
Yes, I'm Sakurano, Dragons Blue!
Please call me Nao-chan!
Yes, I am Purple Purple Kakkaoguru Esky!
Please call me Yuzuki!
Now that you have introduced yourself, I would like to explain the project,
We're going to enjoy finishing the meal together,
There is a red mark on the tip,
The person who draws the red mark on the tip will receive a present!
Yay!
That's important!
From this box, you have to draw what is written on the inside of this box!
Yes!
There might be a cause this time,
Enjoy the dragons!
Delicious!
I hope you enjoy it!
So, I'd like to get started right away,
Team Killer Whale is going to celebrate with a nice toast here,
May I ask you to make a toast?
Please do!
Don't we get to make a nice toast?
No!
I'm a little nervous!
Then, everyone, please hold the toast in your right or left hand!Then everyone, please hold your shakes in your right or left hand!
It doesn't matter which one!
Left hand!
Oh, with your right hand!
It doesn't matter!
Takaneko and Team Orca meet today!
Yes!
We met today!
I would be very happy if we could further deepen our bond to make the live show a success!
Please get to know each other!
Seino!
Cheers to Sparkles!
Cheers to sparkles!
You're too far away from Kirakira, we can't be on the same end of the line,
I'm gonna use Wi-Fi!
This is Studio Orca's Wi-Fi!
Wi-Fi!
Wi-Fi is so cute!
If it's Takaneko, who's going to make a toast?
Who would it be?
Mikuro?
It wasn't Mikuro!
Oh, that's right!
I only have a personal toast name.
A personal toast?
Not just any toast,
It's called "Gachikoi Factory.
Is it for distribution?
A celebration of delivery?
On the anniversary of a music video that has been viewed millions of times,
I do the "Gachikoi Factory" with fans.
What!
Members do it sometimes, don't they?
Yes, they do!
I've never done it before.
I want to!
What about Marumaru's place?
How do you do it?
You guys just remember high, low, and equal.
High, low, and equal.
High?
High, deep, equal.
Ah! That makes sense.
How are you feeling?
High!
And your love for Chicory?
Deep!
And your love?
Equal!
Cheers!
Bye-bye!
The finishing touches have arrived!
Bye bye!
I'd like to eat it, but then I'd like you to eat it in order, starting with Sasachan.
Sasachan!
I'm nervous.
Go for it!
You're the second one.
I love cheese,
I'll have some.
Looks delicious.
You're going to eat it?
Don't get it dirty. Be careful.
Bon appétit.
Looks delicious.
Everyone eats so much.
Still not coming out?
You don't get it yet?
I'm still trying to figure it out.
When the easy Aku comes,
I'll win.
How's it going? How's it going?
How's it going?
What's up?
That one?
Oh!
That's great.
I see.
Unfortunately, this one was delicious.
Next, I'll go with Hinaha.
I will have my favorite sweet potato.
I like its taste, so I'll go with small.
Bon appétit.
This!
This, this much.
Ah!
Congratulations!
I'm off!
Did you smell a hit?
I'll take it.
Bon appétit!
I'm off!
Let's see what we get.
It's good.
You rap and compliment the other person?Complimenting the other person with rap?
LOL!
What?
Really?
I'll give you a compliment.
I'm off.
Yo lift!
Haru is so cute today!
Frog hair looks great on you!
Her eyes are big and beautiful!
Tear ducts are so cute!
Haru-chan is so cute!
Thank you for your hard work
So this is how you're coming?
Eh?
Huh? But the sweets might still come.
That's right.
That's for sure.
Wow, that's great. You got one right off the bat.
Well, it's springtime.
I'll go with red ginger.
Ooh.
I love red ginger.
Bon appétit.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
What?
Your makeup is red.
I don't know.
Chicken.
It's red for a chicken.
Oh!
That was fun.
Okay, let's go next.
I'd like to go next.
Which one do you want?
I love birds.
I'll have the bird.
Oh!
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm gonna have to put some sauce on it.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Hang in there!
Good luck, everyone!
I'm next.
Last week.
I don't know... I'll take this one.
I always eat Shabbos.
I'll have the shrimp.
Oh!
Bon appétit!
Yes, I'll eat with you.
Here you go.
Bon appétit.
Oh!
Oh, you're going to eat?
I'm a little unprepared.
I don't need it.
Honoka, I'm ready.
Bon appétit.
I've been trying to get some good luck this year, too.
Brussels sprouts!
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
Raah.
You want me to bring it last?
I'm waiting.
Race you?
What should we eat?
I think I'll have a quail.
Quail sounds good.
I'll put this on, too.
But it's good.
Well then...
If you say so...
If you like...
I'll have some.
Bon appétit!
Wow.
Yum!
It's so cute!
Oh, my God, it's so good!
It's so good.
You're a girl all of a sudden.
Kanochuu ha...
A switch.
I'm going to hit the switch!
Let's see what we can get
Let's see what's coming out
Ten minutes.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Amazon Harajuku Prefecture!
Conscience!Conscience!
Yay!!!
I'm so happy!
We did it!
We won!
Yesternut!
What should I get?
This is a Takaneko Pankan!
That's right.
Can you do it?
Bon appétit!
Oh!
Yay!
We did it!
That was so much fun!
Oh, my God! What is it now?
Ta-da!
A real kissy face from a situation actor.
Wow!
Yay!
Yes!
What was that?
Okay, I'm gonna make this real.
On my way home from Scouts.
I confessed my feelings
I confessed my feelings to him.
Wow!
That's great.
Can I ask you a favor?
Kiss face?
Lynn! Lynn!
Ready!
Three, two, one.
Senpai, I like you. Please go out with me.
Yay!
That was great!
I want Shaki-chan to come out.
I don't want to get out too much.
Let's go with the flow.
What shall we do?
What can I get you?
Cheese!
I'll have some cheese.
Wow!
Yes!
Nice flow.
Good flow
Fish exhibition
Frog Song
Wa cree
Mountain hemp
Old age
Is everyone on the right having a good time?
It was really a good day for me to meet you all today.
It was a great day!
It's my pleasure.
With this song, I'm graduating.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to end with a song that I'll always remember.
I'd like to end with this song.
Please listen to it.
Frog Song
You'll hear the frog song.
Let's sing it together
Kero kero kero kero Gobble gobble gobble
Good day, see you again *
Boo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo
I don't know how many of you are out there, and I don't know what you put in, but there are four of us.
I don't know what I put in... four.
But now, now, now, I've made red in a row...
I might be able to go to Bach, but I might not yet...
hmm...
full
vinibra 45
full vinibra 45
car
I'll have the meat.
Okay, I'll have the meat, then.
Wow!
That's good.
I want you to listen to me.
I want you to listen.
Bon appétit.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
Wait a minute. Aren't you in high school already?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no. Here we go.
I'm going to go make some cheese.
Oh!
Bon appétit.
What?
Cheese!
Of course!
I was in high school.
I was thrown.It was thrown.
What?
Well then...
Show Yuko which one you like.
Yes.
Umeshiso.
Yes, I ate it.
Bon appétit.
Normal.
Bon appétit!
So cute!
But it's pretty big.
Yes, it's good.
Bon appétit.
Wow!
Yeah!
We won!
Congratulations!
I'm happy for you. I'm not happy for you.
But it's got a sweet gif.
Sweet gifty.
It's over!
Ugh!
I hate this title.
What title?
Ugh! It's a comedy!
What is it? You're supposed to put that in there.
Let's hear it!
Let me hear it!
What do you like?
What? It's so hard!
I don't like this new song title. What title?
What kind of title?
It's so bad!
I'm sorry!
I like it when you get excited.
Wait a minute.
Can I go now?
I don't like the title of this new song!
It's "Lovely Pripyrizaemon"!
No!
It's so cute!
It makes sense!
No!
I'd like to see it if you could pretend to be cute or something.
Lovely, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty.
But if it's too cute
I'm not sure if it's too cute or not...
I'm listening in Zaemon
I'm listening in Zaemon!
I'm very particular about this!
Because it's Zaemon.
He's got a sword and everything!
You have a sword?
I'm selling it!
It's got shields and stuff!
How many did you get in one round? Five!
Five!
That's a lot!
There's a lot left!
I only got one.
I'm counting on you, Sawa-chan!
Lentil!
Delicious!
All right! Here we go!
Everyone?
We're done!
Thank you!
You did a great comedy!
You want to do a comedy?
Oh! The moon!
Oh!
Right?
Yeah!
He came inside with me!
Oh! Inside!
You could have come inside with me!
What!
We had till noon and I got Yusaki's heart!
Ha-ha-ha!
So...
I'm sad, but...
But this is the end of the Takaneko part!
Yes!
We will do this again at Team Saki.
Please look forward to the rest of the story!
That's all! That's all for the Kushiage Party!
Yay!
It was fun!